family what I have to tell you You're going
familia lo que os tengo que contar Vais
to freak out pay attention eh Look Javier Oliveira enough is enough
a flipar atentos eh Mira Javier oliveira
with the
ya está bien ya está bien con la
cancer association and the 240 who don't
asociación del cáncer y los 240 que no
have
tienen
any you are so so selfish so so so
ningún eres tan tan egoísta tan tan tan
agony that it's incredible that in a
agonía que es increíble que en un
space that is doing your live you
espacio que está haciéndote tu directo
are taking advantage of a space where there
estás aprovechá de un espacio donde
are a lot of people who don't
donde hay un montón de gente que no le
give a damn about what you are saying
importa un pijo lo que tú estás diciendo
and on top of that you bring this out to throw me
y encima sacas esto para echarme a mi
out I'm tired of telling you and
tierra estoy cansada de decirte y de
telling everyone but tomorrow
decir a todo el mundo pero mañana lo
I will say it in my
diré en mi
live you have no shame you
directo del no tienes verguenza no
have no shame to say that I kept
tienes vergüenza de decir que me quedé
money from the cancer association I
con dinero de la asociación del cáncer
'm tired I'm tired let's see let's see let's
estoy cansada estoy cansada vamos a ver
see let's see but it's not like this
ver vamos a ver pero es que esto no es
I'm not saying that this space Electra
así yo no digo que este space ya Electra
wants but I'm not going to let this
quiere pero yo no voy a dejar que este
space around Javi wait for me what the
space entor a Javi espérate se me qué
[ __ ] is this guy it's taking too long guy the
[__] [__] esto tío se p tardea tío el
context of this so that you understand
contexto de esto para que me entendáis
is that the other day we were in a space
es que el otro día estábamos en un space
I in the  salsería Okay and we were in a
yo en la salsería Vale y estábamos en un
Twitter space but talking about a
space de Twitter pero hablando de un
topic that I don't know about suddenly she was
tema que no sé yo por de repente le
interested in Peppa but we were
interesaba la Peppa pero estábamos
talking about
hablando de
cryptocurrencies, cryptocurrencies
criptomonedas de
okay it was a
criptomonedas vale era space de
cryptocurrency space because these people who
criptomoneda porque esta gente los que
opened the space were criticizing
abrieron el space estaban criticando al
Dallas with the cryptocurrency that he created and the
Dallas con la criptomoneda que creó y
whole story Okay so I
toda la historia esa Vale entonces yo
had some information that I wanted to give
tenía unas informaciones que quería dar
there and Peppa was there there was Peppa there was Tania there was
allí y estaba allí la Peppa estaba la
Pilar
Peppa estaba la Tania estaba la Pilar
Vera there are all these people who
Vera estan toda esta gente que de
suddenly are very interested in the world of
repente les interesa mucho el mundo de
cryptocurrencies I don't understand
las criptomonedas yo no entiendo el por
why but while I was
qué pero mientras que estaba yo
arguing with the people in the space okay
discutiendo con la gente del space vale
in I was inside Peppa interrupts
en yo estaba dentro la Peppa interrumpe
and enters the Space to say that my
y entra en el Space para decir que mi
sound is very bad and that it is
sonido se escucha muy mal y que eso es
a lack of respect because I am
una falta de respeto porque yo estoy
monetizing Total since we were
monetizando Total que ya que estábamos
talking about bad arts and bad
hablando de malas artes y malas
practices with the issue of money from this
prácticas con el tema del dinero de esto
and that, well I told these
y de lo otro pues yo les dije a esta
people that they had already invited Peppa on
gente que ya habían invitado a Peppa en
several occasions during this week to the
varias ocasiones durante esta semana al
live to the space I said Hey what would you
directo al space les dije Oye qué os
think if a person opened a
parecería que una persona abra un
live in the live ask for donations and
directo en el directo pida donaciones y
said that  they're going to go for cancer and then they
diga que van a ir para el cáncer y luego
forget to give them to the association
se les olvide darlas a la asociación
okay And then the pppa came in this
vale Y entonces ya la pppa entró de esta
way that you've heard I
forma que habéis escuchado
'm not doing it here I'm not going to let
no estoy haciendo aquí no voy a dejar
this space anymore Electra wants it but I'm
que este space ya Electra quiere pero yo
not going to let this space get in the way of
no voy a dejar que este space se entor a
Javi Oliveira and his content I'm not going
Javi oliveira y a su contenido yo no voy
to let this space get in the way of Javi
a dejar que este space se entor a Javi
Oliveira and his content I know the spaces
oliveira y Su contenido di sab los space
are about me But oh well it's okay
tratan sobre mí Pero bueno no pasa nada
occupational jinx if when I
gafes del oficio si cuando yo de
mute and continue talking about the same subject
silencie y sigue hablando del mismo tema
with jav Ah thank God
con lo de jav Ah gracias a Dios ya se
this one is gone look at Mrs. Peppa is that
fue este mira lo de la señora Peppa es
supposedly she
que supuestamente ella
asked No nobody kicked him out he left
pidió No nadie lo echó se
no he didn't disconnect he left I don't know if he
fue no no se desconectó se fue no sé si
left
se fue
because okay well there it fell my
porque vale pues ahí se cayó se me ha
live stream was cut off forgive me I have to
cortado el directo perdonarme tengo que
fix that because I really don't know very
arreglar eso que realmente no sé muy
well how to fix it I think it's a matter
bien cómo arreglarlo creo que es tema
of like when I plug in when
de o sea cuando enchufo cuando
we plug in certain things at the same time
enchufamos ciertas varias cosas a la vez
at home the
en casa como que se salta la
light goes out I imagine it's because of the limit for
luz me imagino que sea por el límite por
protection some move like that I have no
protección alguna movida de esa no tengo
[ __ ] idea but I have  that I have to call and and
ni [__] idea pero tengo que llamar y y
that they level it no Or the or whatever
que me lo nivelen no O lo o lo que sea
no what the [ __ ] what the [ __ ] because they
no qué putada qué putada porque nos ha
cut off the live and we had almost 3000
cortado el directo y teníamos casi 3000
people here but well They'll go in or
personas aquí pero bueno Irán entrando o
not eh Maybe they'll send people to
no eh A lo mejor hos mandab gente para
bed we'll see no but I wanted to
la cama ya veremos no pero he querido
put that again which was where we had
poner eso otra vez que era por donde nos
left off also so that now
habíamos quedado también para que ahora
the kid when I cut the extracts and
el chaval cuando corte los extractos y
so on today it went down for several Jai no
demás hoy se le ha caído a varios Jai no
no but it didn't drop my
no pero a mí no se me ha caído el
live eh my power went out or I mean it's
directo eh se me ha cortado la la luz o
like it jumps you know I have to
sea es como que salta sabes lo tengo que
fix it because in the end that's
arreglar porque al final eso es por por
because of the contracted power that I will have
por la potencia contratada que le habré
set less limits of Let's see it doesn't happen to me
puesto menos límites de A ver no me pasa
much it doesn't happen to me much also it's
mucho no me pasa mucho también es
when when you plug certain things in at the
cuando cuando enchufas ciertas cosas a
same time that the heating is on
la vez que está puesta la la calefacción
not this week you're especially
no esta semana andas especialmente
tamer but tamer cool it's the only
domador pero domador fresco es el único
reason why I can
motivo por el cual
stand cinema Thank you very much what I am
soporto cine Muchas gracias lo que si os
going to ask you please as you come
voy a pedir por favor conforme vayáis
in to hit the like button Okay
entrando que le deis al botón de like Ok
and
y
also we have lost how superchat were
además hemos perdido el cuán superchat
in the ret ties that cont contract
iban en el ret ties que cont contratar
more power I already know that I have to
más potencia Ya lo sé que tengo
contract more power But why
contratar más potencia Pero por qué por
why Because it will be very high or I don't know The
qué Porque será muy alta o no sé La
Movida I don't know The
Movida no sé La
Movida I don't know let's see I explained to him one
Movida no sé a ver yo le expliqué en su
day what I have what I do what is
día lo que tengo lo que hago lo que tal
and they gave me what they what they
y me pusieron lo que ellos lo que ellos
saw I don't know but in the end you pay I mean
vieran no sé pero al final tú pagas o
you pay based on what you spend no matter
sea tú pagas en base a lo que gasten no
what you contract if That
qué más da lo que contrates si Eso ya
depends on what you spend I don't understand
depende de lo que gastes no entiendo
how that works I mean I'm Lego I'm
cómo funciona eso o sea soy Lego soy
Lego eh I'm warning you that I'm Lego I would
Lego eh os lo aviso que soy Lego
probably make a mistake I didn't 17
seguramente metería la pata yo no 17
super chat we had Well nothing
super chat llevábamos Pues nada los
we've lost them Oh
hemos perdido Oh
F Oh
F Oh
F you have to add up The power of the
F tienes que sumar La potencia de los
devices that he uses no [ __ ] idea damn damn They wo
aparatos que usa ni [__] idea
n't be tying your accounts
[__] No te estarán atando tus cuentas
ironically they are now hacking the
irónico están ahora jaqueando los
accounts because that's very interesting accounts
cuentas porque eso muy interes cuentas
people are very interested in
les interesa mucho a la gente lo las
my accounts Thank you very much Carmen Thank you
cuentas mías Muchas gracias Carmen
very much Salomé Thank you very much
Muchas gracias Salomé Muchas gracias
Giorgio What a shame [ __ ] I'm late and with a haha
Giorgio Qué pena [__] llego tarde y con
face a kiss a kiss Carmen
jaa cara de naas un beso un beso Carmen
well  you got the context Peppa
bueno habéis cogido el contexto la Peppa
suddenly came in So I put that
entró de repente Entonces yo puse ese
example, it's not that innocent example, not
ejempl yo no es ese ejemplo inocente no
about the 240 issue and Peppa
sobre el tema de los 240 y la Peppa
went into a fit and got really angry Yes
entró en brote y se cabre muchísimo Sí
David then we go to the salseria
David luego nos vamos para la salsería
Peppa opened a lot and well
abrió muchísimo la Peppa y y bueno
we had a mini debate there that didn't last long
tuvimos ahí un mini debate que duró poco
but well I'll put it to you and we react
pero bueno os lo pongo y lo reaccionamos
okay but the thing is that
vale peroa Ya va la cuestión es que
according to what I heard in a live broadcast
según lo que yo escuché en algún directo
of him, he says that you never handed it in and that they
de él dice que tú nunca lo entregaste y
had to throw it in your face so
que tuvieron que sacártelo en cara para
that you would later
que tú luego lo
hand it in, who says that Javi has
entregaras eso quién lo dice Javi ha
produced evidence that who says that Javi
sacado pruebas eso quién lo dice Javi
says eh so it was me who said
dice eh o sea que fui yo el que dijo
okay it was me who said that Peppa no, she did
vale que fui yo el que dijo que Peppa no
n't give the money the 240 okay she
no dio el dinero los 240 vale se los
kept it for 7 months she held it she
quedó durante 7 meses los holde los
held it for 7 months and
holde los holde durante 7 meses y ya
when her friends threw it in her
cuando sus amigos se lo echaron en
face then she ran out one Monday
cara entonces fue corriendo un lunes por
morning to donate it first thing in the
la mañana a donarlo a primera hora de la
morning okay that's what Javi says and says he's
mañana vale que eso lo dice Javi y dice
produced some evidence man of course what the
ha sacado alguna prueba hombre claro qué
hell am I going to produce if I  I didn't go to donate
[__] voy a sacar si yo no fui a donar lo
you did it take it out yourself take it out that you
fuiste tú sácalo tú sácalo tú de que lo
donated it in its day Peppa what the [ __ ] do I have to take
donaste en su día Peppa yo qué [__]
out? I'm not there we
tengo que sacar yo no estoy ahí nosotros
did our job which was to call
hicimos nuestro trabajo que fue Llamar a
the soc okay We called the soc
a la soc vale Nosotros llamamos a la soc
and more people called the soc now we're
y más gente llamó a la soc ahora lo
going to
vamos a
see it No no that's why you're here so you can
ver No no por eso es que tú estás aquí
explain it of course Javi
para que lo expliques claro es que Javi
never produced any proof of anything he never produced
nunca sacó pruebas de nada nunca sacó
any proof what the [ __ ] am I going to take out? I'm going to take it out
prueba de nada qué [__] voy a sacar yo
You're the one who has to
sácalo tú Tú eres la que tienes que
take out that you donated it 7 months before, talk to
sacar que lo donaste 7 meses antes habla
friend, for example, called the association
amiga ejemp llamó a la asociación
[Music]
[Música]
and that no that she says that Tania didn't call no no no no no
y que no que dice que Tania no llamó no
what she says that Tania didn't call
no no no no que dice que Tania no llamó
but this What
pero esto Qué
is it that you ran away that's uncertain Mon
es que te fuiste corri eso es incierto
morning donate it that's
lun por la mañana donarlo eso es
uncertain Tania never said that Tania
incierto Tania nunca dijo eso Tania
never said that let's
nunca dijo eso a
see a little yes no she says t she never said that let's
ver un poco sí no dice t nunca dijo eso
see a little if she said it no let's see okay
a ver un poco si lo dijo no a ver vale
because okay as they were passing the
porque vale como estaban pasando la
girl I asked girl do you give me
chica yo preg chica me da usted
authorization to show this call and she
autorización para mostrar esta llamada y
told me that  No, I don't give you authorization,
me dijo que no no le doy autorización
okay, perfect, and I'll put it. No, no,
vale perfecto y lo pongo no no
authorization to show the call.
autorización para mostrar la llamada
Who's lying? I'm not accusing anyone of lying,
quién miente yo no acus a nadie de menir
but I was like everyone else,
sino que yo estaba como todo el mundo la
most of them, doubting because you say they are
mayoría dudando porque dices son
public, donations are not public,
públicas las donaciones no son públicas
data protection, transparency,
la protección de datos transparencia en
anyway, and well. Well, I say that's what they
fin y pues Bueno digo eso es lo que me
told me. So if there are people
comunican a m Entonces si hay personas
who have called, how have they managed to obtain
que han llamado Cómo han logrado obtener
data? Because they had left it to me, very
datos Porque a m me lo haban dejado mu
clear that they all had the
Claro que todas llevaban el protocolo
confidentiality protocol and they
protocolo de confidencialidad y me
told me. In addition, I put it. They have
dijeron además lo pongo es más me han
told me that the receipt is sent by
dicho que el comprobante se envía por
email and that the person who donates can
email y que la persona que dona puede
print it but that they will send it to me by email.
imprimirlo pero que me envían por mail
This is what they tell me on the first
Esto es lo que me dicen en la primera
call. I also called a phone that they
llamada también llam un teléfono que lo
answer, it's like you hang up all the time,
cogen es como que te colgas todo el rato
all the time, all the time, no, and today I
todo el rato todo el rato no y hoy he
called again, today I called again and
vuelto a llamar hoy he vuelto a llamar y
today I
hoy he vuelto a
called again. Sorry for the interruption, grandpa,
llamar Perdón la interrupción abuelito
the light is because your
lo de la luz es porque tu tablero
electrical panel inside the house has
eléctrico dentro de casa es de voltaje
very low voltage, you should buy one with more
muy bajito debes comprar una con más
capacity and that's it. You're speaking to me in
capcidad y listo me estás hablando en
Chinese. Thank you very much, nii, but I don't
chino Muchas gracias nii pero yo no
have  I have no idea about that, let's see, what I know is
tengo ni idea de eso a ver yo lo que sé
that the heating in the house came
que la califacción esta de la casa venía
with the house. I mean, no, it's not a
con la casa O sea no no es una
heater that I installed, it's this one
calefacción que yo instale sea es esta
that's on the ceiling. No, I don't understand
que está por el techo No yo no entiendo
electronics or anything, I mean, I'll call, I have to call, I have to
de electrónica ni de ni de nada o sea yo
call, but it's been a while now. Uh, it's
llamar pero ya hace tiempo Eh me han
happened to me a few times, it happens that tomorrow I
pasado unas cuantas veces lo pasa que
forget, tomorrow I don't
luego mañana ya se me olvida mañana no
know what you know. I won't call tomorrow, but uh, back
sé qué sabis Ya mañana no llamo pero eh
in the day, well, I explained to him. Well, look,
yo en su día pues le expliqué Pues mira
the house has this, it has that, and I
la casa tiene esto tiene lo otro y y yo
usually work doing this and that,
suelo trabajar haciendo esto y haciendo
not what I use more than anything, no,
lo otro no lo que uso más que nada no y
and there are times when it goes off, there are times that it doesn't, I don't
y hay veces que salta hay veces que no
know, honestly, I think it
no lo sé la verdad creo que son
depends on the specific things
dependiendo de las cosas en concretas
that are plugged in at the same time, but I have no
que estén a la vez enchufada pero ni
[ __ ] idea. I've made four calls, I
[__] idea cuatro llamadas he hecho cl yo
understand that if that's what's in the house, the
entiendo que si eso viene en la casa la
house should be prepared for that, no,
casa debería estar preparado para eso no
at 2:18 PM at 2:33 PM and I've been on the phone for 6
a las 14:18 a las 14:33 y he hablado 6
minutes and 11 seconds, okay, who are you
minutos y 11 segundos vale quién me
telling me here? Let's
dicen aquí a
see what they're telling me
ver qué me dice
here that they're not going to give me
aquí que no me van a dar
information.
información a
Verene is having a fight with the microphone that is
verene tiene una pelea con el micro que
freaking out about this donation and the
flipa esto de esta donación de y la
controversy and the mess that they couldn't know
polémica y el follo que no podían saber
the person who is assisting me couldn't know
la persona que me atiende no podía saber
but that they were aware so well is he aware
pero que estaban al tanto entonces bueno
knows or doesn't he know and they tell me
está al tanto sabe o no sabe y me dicen
that this is in the
que esto está en el departamento
legal department and This is what they told me today
jurídico y Esto me lo han dicho a mí hoy
okay that it is being handled by the
vale que está lo está llevando ya el
legal department that
departamento jurídico que se han
some videos have been presented
presentado unos vídeos se han expuesto
things have been exposed and indeed indeed the
cosas y efectivamente efectivamente el
day that he shows the paper the afternoon that he
día que muestra el papel la tarde que
shows the paper
muestra el papel
Ah that day was when he donated and the worst
Ah ese día fue cuando donó y el el peor
mistake you made Pepa Beltrán was doing
error que tuviste [__] Beltrán fue hacer
that Direct was doing that Direct What a
ese Direct fue hacer ese Direct Qué
coincidence that Ángel wasn't there I
casualidad que no estaba Ángel yo me me
wonder if you had been Angel you
pregunto si hubieras estado Ángel
would have shown the paper better if
hubieras enseñado el papel mejor que no
Ángel hadn't been there I don't understand this
hubiera estado Ángel esto no lo entiendo
now okay I understood it later what if
ahora vale Yo s lo he entendí después lo
Angel had been there why
de que si hubiera estado ángel por qué
Because if Angel had been there
Porque si hubiera estado Ángel
surely They would have done something crazy we will
seguramente Hubieran hecho una locura
never know But well the only one who
nunca lo sabremos Pero bueno el único
said it you that you had called the
que lo dijiste tú que habías llamado el
only one who said it you that you had
único que lo dijiste tú que habías
called tells a lie many people called
llamado dice a mentira llamó mucha gente
not even not even just Tania eh
ni siquiera ni siquiera solo la Tania eh
Ni  even if it was just Tania who called a lot of
Ni siquiera solo la Tania llamó mucha
people who weren't YouTubers, people are
gente que no era youtuber la gente
worried about the money they had donated.
preocupa por su dinero que habían donado
How could it be that she didn't say it, but one
Cómo que no Cómo que no lo dijo pero una
thing they have. That recorded call or something, of
cosa tienen Esa llamada grabada o algo
course we do have it, and apart from that, we
claro que sí la tenemos y aparte que la
also have Tania
tenemos También tenemos a la Tania
recorded on her live stream telling it. Of course,
grabada en su directo contándolo Claro
yes. I mean, what a double chin, kid,
que sí O sea pues vaya papada chaval
trust you, Tania, Tania is
fíate tu la Tania que la Tania es
my enemy, okay, I mean, I mean, look
enemiga mía vale o sea sea fíjate tú por
where this man is coming out now,
dónde está saliendo este hombre ahora
but I come out wherever I want, I mean,
pero que salgo por donde me dé la gana o
trust you where
sea fíate tú por dónde está saliendo
this man is coming out now. Now I'm coming out for what it
este hombre Ahora estoy saliendo por lo
is, you're denying one thing that you're not
que es estás negando una cosa que no me
going to deny me, you're never going to deny me, pppa, you
vas a negar nunca me la vas a negar pppa
took donations, 240 bucks, whatever
cogiste donaciones 240 pavos lo que
the ise were, and what H until
fueran los ise y te lo que H hasta que
your friends
tus amigos lo
snitch on you don't get to, it's the same thing, it
chivaronas no llegan a es lo mismo te
hits you, who knows, you know, man, already
pega vete to a saber sabes hombre ya
Peppa, there we met the real Peppa.
Peppa ahí conocimos a la verdadera Peppa
That's your
Esa es tu
condition, you want content for your
condición quieres contenido para tu
live stream. No, what the [ __ ], what mantra is this, what nonsense are you doing?
directo No qué [__] que mantra este que
You want content for
chorradas estas quieres contenido para
your live stream if you're the one who's there.
tu directo si eres tú la que estás ahí
appearing she was Like a liar man
apareciendo quedó Como mentirosa hombre
Like a liar is the least r because I
Como mentirosa es lo mínimo r porque yo
a person who takes money for a
una persona que coge dinero para una
cancer association and does not give it if they are not
asociación del cáncer y no lo da si no
reminded man
se lo recuerdan hombre por
please laera now needs a little
favor laera necesita ahora un poquito
more instead of token instead of so much
más en vez de token en vez de tanto
token and so much Christ Hey but the virgin
token y tanto Cristo Oye pero la virgen
Mara
Mara
veng we know each other we are talking about
veng nos conocemos estamos hablando de
token you invested those 240 for 7
token tú invertiste esos 240 durante 7
months did they pay off or not
meses te rentaron o no te
look Precisely it wasn't
rentaron Mira Precisamente es que ni
even 2 I let you say to you
siquiera eran 2 yo te dejado decir a ti
240 240 how much Peppa was I said that what I
240 240 cuánto eran Peppa yo dije que lo
took from there Yeah taking away what
que cogiera de allí Ajá quitando lo que
YouTube takes away which is 40% what happens
quita YouTube que es el 40% lo que pasa
is that I have let you beat there say
es que yo te he dejado batir ahí decir
things because you say them like that you
las cosas porque tú las dices así tú las
you tell a lie you repeat it one day and another
tú dices una mentira la repites un día y
day and another day you send tuario to
otro día y otro día mandas a tuario a
repeat it repeat it repeat it repeat it
repetirla repetirla repetirla repetirla
what are you going to do in those 7 months how how that
cuá goeast en esos 7 meses cómo cómo que
How many holde Ase 7 months holde the 240
Cuántos holde Ase 7 meses holde los 240
understand I want to ask a question Javi
entiendas yo qui hacer una pregunta Javi
before that  change the subject and this and
antes de que cambies de tema y este y
this eh before I change the subject
este eh antes de que cambie de tema
I have to ask you a question in your
tengo que hacerte una pregunta en tu
live we didn't pay attention because
directo no le echamos cuenta pues
we were discussing something and that
estamos discutiendo una cosa y llegó ese
character came and what he wanted to say then he
personaje que lo que quería decir luego
said it Wait I think I left it
lo dijo Espera creoo que lo he dejado
open here I didn't leave it
abierto no lo he dejado
open Oh no I didn't leave it open or is it
abierto Ay no lo dejado abierto o es
for the kids look
para la chavalería mirar
what the creature wanted to do
que quería hacer la criatura
Look let me ask a question and I'm
Mira me dejáis hacer una pregunta y me
leaving This was later I mean at the
voy ya Esto fue después O sea en el
moment we continued discussing
momento nosotros seguimos discutiendo la
Peppa and I we changed the
Peppa y yo ya cambiamos el
subject it's 15 seconds it's not even a
tema son 15 segundos ni siquiera es un
debate Let's see Javi is like an
debate A ver es que a ver Javi es como
expert in gossip and crypts he doesn't have a
experto en salseo y en criptas no tiene
clue himself he said it then to me
ni idea mismo lo ha dicho entonces a m
both his part and mine have
tanto parte de su como mío han
asked ask several things And
preguntado preguntar varias cosas Y
above all one and I wanted to ask
sobre todo una y quería preguntarle a
Javi if with those 10500 that he won from
Javi que si con esos 10500 que ganó de
pambi if he has used them to put to
pambi si los ha usado para pon para
put B the girl I asked the
ponerse B la chica Yo Le pregun a la
girl do you give me authorization for this
chica me da usted autorización para esta
call and she said no I don't give her
llamada y me dijo que no no le doy
authorization okay perfect and I put it she doesn't give
autorización vale perfecto y lo pongo no
me authorization to show jumped
me autorización para mostrar saltado
damn  well anyway it's a joke to
[__] bueno en fin es una gracia para
say that I have gotten hair and that I have
decir que me he puesto pelo y que me sí
used them to get hair to
los ha usado para ponerse pelo para
get botx or to have surgery the torch already
ponerse botx o operarse la tocha ya
asking papeado and Well no no
quiring papeado e Bueno pues no no
because because the operations are
porque no porque las operaciones son
previous the 10 500 were later
anteriores los 10 500 fueron posteriores
but well maybe you left us a
pero bueno a lo mejor nos habéis dejado
deposit like Dallas yes I don't know like
de depósito como Dallas sí no sé como
Dallas I recommend that you invest by
Dallas te recomiendo que inviertas por
the way Maybe you earn something too to
cierto A lo mejor tú ganas algo también
do something for yourself Yeah I don't know if you want to if you want to
para para hacerte algo s no s si quiere
throw that he's
la si quier echar
my age eh I mean I didn't know
que tiene mi edad eh o sea yo no sabía
that I just found out that he was my
eso me enteré hace poco que tenía mi
age which is like [ __ ] But well I
edad que es como hostias Pero bueno
was trying to interrupt that debate
Estaba intentando interrumpir ese debate
to say that I do
para decir
n't know when you're in second
eso no sé cuando estás en segundo de
grade or something
primaria o cosa
like that because you say them like that you you tell
así porque tú las dices así tú tú dices
a lie you repeat it one day and another day
una mentira la repites un día y otro día
and another day you
y otro día
send repeat repeat it
mandas repetir repetirla repetirla
repeat it but how many goldee in those 7
repetirla pero cuántos goldee en esos 7
months How How much Hold dease 7
meses Cómo Cómo que cuánto Hold dease 7
months holde and the
meses holde and los
240 qui ask a question before I
240 qui hacer una pregunta antes de que
change the subject in your live he's like a
cambi tema en tu directo está como un
child not like that when Oh look look look what
niño no así cuando Ay mira mira mira lo
what am I going to do I'm going to interrupt to
que voy a hacer Voy a interrumpir para
say Haha fart fart poop
decir Jaja pedo pedo caca
ass your live stream you're making a
culo tu directo te estás haciendo un
piece of content that's [ __ ] and I can
pedazo de contenido que te cagas y te
hear you very badly and And this is very little
escucha muy mal y Y esto es muy poco
respect for the people here in space that's what
respeto a la gente de aquí del espacio
Peppa answers you're making
eso lo que contesta Peppa estás haciendo
content and it sounds very
un contenido y se escucha muy
bad okay Peppa the 240 then Tania
mal vale Peppa los 240 entonces la Tania
lied when she said you can put emojis here in
mintió cuando dijo pueden poner aquí en
the chat too you heard guys
el chat también emojis oyeron chicos
only with emojis that are with emojis
solo con emojis que están con emojis
Here not here also in the comments
Aquí no aquí también en los comentarios
all the emojis you want okay come on
todos los emojis que quieran vale venga
Peppa so Nitro can give
Peppa para que Nitro
his opinion when Tania says that the
opine cuando Tania dice que llama la
association calls and the association tells her that
asociación y la asociación le dice que
you went on Monday morning
tú fuiste el lunes por la mañana
running to give the 240 when your
corriendo a dar los 240 cuando tus
friends said that for 7 months you
amigos pusieron que durante 7 meses se
had forgotten to donate them Tania is lying
te habían olvidado donarlos miente Tania
or the association is lying or who's
o miente la asociación o quién
lying only Javi only Javi of course F
miente solo Javi solo Javi claro sea F
you the rush eh the rush It's that I tell her we're
tú el apuro eh el apuro Es que le digo
going to see a lot of people who donated okay the
vamos a ver mucha gente que donó vale la
people who donated Tania who is
gente que donó la Tania que es enemiga
my enemy let's not say she didn't call too I mean no
mía no digamos no llamó también o sea no
no  It was a thing of mine, it's that
no fue una cosa mía es que llamaron
people called, more people called to hire that
gente más gente llamó para contratar esa
information to the soc Why, because
información a la soc Por qué porqueo
when you donate money to an
cuando tú donas un dinero a una
association like this one for cancer,
asociación como es esta del cáncer no
donations are not anonymous, do you
las donaciones no son anónimas me
understand? So I say to him, well, you
entiendes Entonces yo le digo Bueno tú
're telling me that what
me estás diciendo que son mentiras lo
I'm saying is lies, then
que yo estoy diciendo entonces mintió la
Tania lied, she lied, everyone who
Tania mintió mintieron todos los que
called lied, what happened? She left, she left, she's on
llamaron qué pasó se fue Se fue está
mute, Mrs. pppa, she left, she left
silenciada la señora pppa se fue Se fue
pppa is looking for the paper, it's not there, it's there,
pppa está buscando el papel no está ahí
no Ah, but it is, it's there but it's
está ahí no Ah pero está está ahí pero
muted, it's muted, you're cool Right
está silenciado está silenciado estás
now Peppa is gone, Peppa, I do
onda Ahora mismo Peppa se fue Peppa yo
n't understand anything, Peppa is gone.
no entiendo nada se fue la
I also wanted to ask a question
Peppa Yo igual quería hacer una pregunta
about Pambi before the topic ends, just in case,
de pambi antes de que termine el tema
if I can, but Peppa, of course,
por las dudas si puedo pero Peppa claro
go ahead, Peppa doesn't want to talk.
adelante adelante Peppa no quiere hablar
Nobody can force her, go ahead, she's gone. In
Nadie puede obligar
short, she's been dedicated
adelante se fue Total que se ha dedicado
to doing live shows these
a a hacer directos estos
days saying that she had to
días diciendo que es que tuvo que
abandon the live show because, look, look
abandonar el directo por que mira mira
how she did live the other day, poor
cómo hizo directo el otro día pobre
Peppa, poor
Peppa pobre
Peppa, I mean, let's see, or I mean, you
Peppa o sea vamos a ver oa o sea te
know what Peppa did, not the extra, of
sabes lo que hizo Peppa no el exra claro
course, because I heard it.  in your stuff
claro porque lo escuché en en tu cosas
when I saw your live streams and you put it here I
cuando veía tus directos y la metes aquí
go look you know what Peppa did and you
yo voy fijaros sabes lo que hizo Peppa y
put it here but what the [ __ ] do you
la metes aquí pero tú qué [__] te has
think you haven't gotten involved you are the
creído no te has metido a ti que eres el
worst bug on the internet and what have I done
peor [__] de internet y yo qué he hecho
or rather what have I done I have done that I have
o sea yo qué he hecho yo he hecho eso yo
done that he says he knows let's see clearly let's
he hecho eso dice dice sab a ver claro a
see It was a space about cryptocurrency
ver Era un eh space sobre criptomoneda
they were playing and questioning what
estaban jugando y cuestionando lo que ha
Dallas has done with cryptocurrencies If
hecho Dallas con las criptomonedas Si la
people have invested money if they haven't
gente ha invertido dinero si no ha
invested money and you take it with your
invertido dinero y coges tú con tu
grapefruit and enter that space you
pomelo y entras en ese space a tú
also put [ __ ] about me and
también meter [__] sobre mí y sobre
Dallas man well if we are talking
Dallas hombre pues si estamos hablando
about an economic issue let's talk about
de un tema económico vamos a hablar de
you that you collected some money
que a ti de que tú recogiste un dinero
that was going to a
que iba para una asociación con el
cancer association and you forgot for 7 months to
cáncer y se te olvidó durante 7 meses
give it holde Ase Give the
darlo lo holde Ase Dale consejo a los
kids
chavales de
investment advice Total
inversión Total
that I am the worst I have never done
que que yo soy la peor yo no he hecho
anything like that Pepa in my life you put it here but
algo así [__] en mi vida metes aquí pero
you what the [ __ ] do you think you have not gotten
tú qué [__] te has creído no te has
involved you are the worst bug on the
metido a ti que eres el peor [__] de
internet No I am not the  worst bug on the
internet No yo no soy el peor [__] de
internet I have not done the things that you
internet yo no he hecho las cosas que
have done you piece of
habéis hecho ustedes pedazo de de
scoundrel he has not put you in and you
Sinvergüenza no te ha metido a ti y la
put it here it means that he wants to restrict your
metes aquí es decir que quiere coart
freedom he wants no no I do not
arme la libertad quiere no no yo no
want to restrict your freedom I want
quiero coarte la libertad yo quiero que
you to give explanations for in 7
tú des las explicaciones de por en 7
months you did not give that
meses no diste ese
money to take the freedom to others
dinero tarle la libertad a los demás de
that I can be or cannot be in a in a in a
que yo pueda estar o no pueda estar en
live for what I
un en un en un directo por lo que yo
did and what you have done and what
hice y lo que has hecho tú y lo que has
you have done and what you have done let's see what I have
hecho tú y lo que has hecho tú a ver qué
done no do not tell your mom
he hecho no no se lo digas a tu mamá
[Laughs]
[Risas]
porpi that is what I have done and Peppa
porpi eso es lo que he hecho y Peppa
wrote a message in
escribirle un mensaje en el
2016 to a friend eh one night going out to
2016 a una amiga eh una noche saliendo
party in which in the
de fiesta en el que ella en la
conversation she is not uncomfortable or there is
conversación no está ni incómoda ni hay
anything
nada
strange
raro
Ah you liked a
Ah a ti te gustaba una niña
chincha girl man I see it a little worse what
chincha hombre lo veo un poco peor lo de
he tried to do to give you the money eh
haberte intentado que dar el dinero eh
Peppa having crazy you for 7 months
Peppa haberte loqueado durante 7 meses
eh I think it is a little worse eh but
eh Me da que es un poco peor eh pero
well that is it that everyone  He
bueno que ya está que a todo el mundo se
can forget us and then you gave it after 7
nos puede olvidar y luego tú a los 7
months, that's it. It's okay,
meses lo diste ya está No pasa
my goodness, what have you done and you say, damn,
mía y lo que has hecho tú y clo dices tú
what have I done? Have I kept
[__] qué he hecho Me he quedado yo más
even more money or what have I scammed from
dinero todavía o qué he estafado yo a la
people? What have I done? I don't know. No, do
gente qué es lo que hecho yo no yo sé no
n't tell your mother,
no se lo digas a tu madre
please. That's
porfi Eso es
all. Wow, look at the atrocities that
todo Wow mir las barbaridades que has
you and the people that you have done,
hecho tú y a la gente que tú has hecho
real damage
daño real
to all of this, I'm left
a todo esto yo me
saying, this isn't happening, this isn't
quedo digo esto no está pasando esto no
happening. I'm left saying, this isn't
está pasando yo me quedo esto no está
happening, this isn't happening. And Peppa,
pasando esto no está pasando y que Peppa
the one who isn't happening, that you got into
el que no está pasando que te metiste en
a space because you're
un space porque estás
[Laughs]
[Risas]
chasing me, grandpa. The truth is that it brought
persiguiéndome abuelo la verdad es que s
out my shame, it brought
me sacó mis vergüenzas
a live broadcast to ask for money for
abrí un directo para pedir dinero para
a cancer association. I opened a
una asociación del cáncer yo abrí un
live broadcast. What I don't understand is how
directo lo que yo no entiendo es cómo ha
the guy had the nerve to take this space
tenido el pomelo tío de [__] este space
and he's putting it on his channel. I mean, do you
y lo está poniendo en su canal O sea os
remember what I told you before? That
acordáis lo que os he dicho antes de que
I think there are a lot of people on the planet
yo creo que en el planeta hay mucha
who are idiots.  idiot You have to
gente que es idiota pues idiota Hay que
be to be on this live show of this
ser para estar en este directo de esta
lady giving you these explanations and you
señora dándote estas explicaciones y tú
swallow mine to give visibility to
tragárnos mío para dar visibilidad al
bone marrow cancer when I was donated
cáncer de médula cuando a mí me donaron
Oh is this bugi or what is it not
los Ay se bugi esto o qué no se le
heard it was bugged Sorry already with all this to
escucha estaba bugado Perdón ya a todo
all this I started to feel
esto a a todo esto yo empecé a sentirme
bad man of course you're not going to feel bad
mal hombre claro no te vas a sentir mal
like they were catching you with the
como que te estaban pillando con el
ice cream cart very bad eh the room started to
helados muy mal eh el salón empezó a
turn me of course eh I started to sob
darme vuelta claro eh empecé a sorar
sweat of course eh my heart was pumping
sudor claro eh el corazón bombeaba
too hard of course and I thought it's
demasiado fuerte claro y pensé me está
giving me it's giving me poor Pepa I'm
dando me está dando pobre [__] me
feeling poor Peppa let's go with
estando pobre Peppa vamos aar con
this I mean she had a
esto O sea le dio un ataque al
heart attack it's giving it it's giving it
corazón le está dando le está dando
just when she has to give the
justo cuando tiene que dar las
explanations of her life because
explicaciones de su vida pues
Peppa here you didn't have an attack look
Peppa aquí no te dio ningún ataque mira
at your little tits and your little tummy son
con tus tetitas y tu barriguita hijo
of
de
a [ __ ] scoundrel why do
u pedazo de sinvergüenza rastrero porque
you look like white you're like a
se te ve así como blanco estás como un
little constipated
poquito así estreñido
oh
uy
oh the attacks why do you have to be
uy los ataques porque hay que ser
[ __ ] this piece of scoundrel
[__] este pedazo de de sinvergüenza
you are an ignorant guy is a son of a
eres un ignorante tío es un hijo de
[ __ ] or  or Oy ar gorfo This one is more than
fruta o o Oy ar gorfo Este sí má que
stupid that one has to be stupid was a
tonto que hay que ser tonto era un
pingado like your friend Javi Oy poor
pingado como tu amigo Javi Oy la pobre
Cowardly
el Cobarde
Angel is not going to give you Botox no and he
Ángel no irá a ponerte botox no y me
tells me that you go to the dentist no Uy How
dice que vas el dentista no Uy Qué
funny you are going to take it up the ass you
graciosa tú te vas a tomar por culo
piece of [ __ ]
pedazo de mendrugo
idiot uy uy u you are very pathetic dude
[__] uy uy u eres muy patético tío
Paw Patrol because you are a
Patrulla canina porque tú eres un
[ __ ]
mindungui
Wash that mouth with
Lávate esa boca con
soap Wash that little mouth with soap Uy you did
jabón Lávate esa boquita con jabón Uy
n't have it
ahí no te daba
there you didn't have an attack eh Peppa
ahí no te daba ningún ataque eh Peppa
how funny you are when you don't have an
qué divertida eres cuando no te dan
attack eh And missing eh Because with
ningún ataque eh Y falta eh Porque con
my wife you also messed with my wife you
mi mujer también te metiste con mi mujer
also messed with and many more things
también te metiste y muchas más cosas
that you have
que has
done a live to ask for
hecho un directo para pedir para lación
cancer relief I opened a live with a
del cáncer yo abrí un directo con un
friend it was hard for me to pronounce those words
amigo me costó pronunciar esas palabras
you don't know how hard it was for me because that was
ustedes no sabéis lo que me costó porque
already starting
ya empezaba aquello
s Javi laughs he enjoys hurting
a s Javi se ríe disfruta haciéndole daño
others Uy Javi How bad Uy
a los demás Uy el Javi Qué malo Uy el
Javi How bad that he is telling me about the
Javi Qué malo que me está diciendo lo de
240 I have it very clear mine who
los 240 lo tengo clarísimo mío que
lost a nephew to
perdió a un sobrino por el cáncer de
bone marrow cancer so what we wanted to give
médula entonces lo que queríamos dar
visibility to bone marrow cancer and for
visibilidad al cáncer de médula y que la
people to give it you wanted to give cancer you
gente diera le queríais dar cáncer de le
wanted to give visibility to cancer
queríais dar visibilidad al cáncer
you wanted to give visibility to the
ustedes le quisiste dar visibilidad a al
issue of cancer but what you have not
tema del cáncer pero a lo que no le has
wanted to give visibility to is what you
querido dar visibilidad es a lo que
have done with the donation you have not
habéis hecho con La donación a eso no le
given visibility to that well that
habéis dado visibilidad bueno que que
someone had the possibility of being
tuviera la posibilidad alguien de
saved with the issue of
salvarse con con el tema de La donación
bone marrow donation when I yes well if
de médula cuando yo sí sí pues si
someone had the possibility of being
alguien tuviera la posibilidad de
saved with your donation Let's
salvarse con La donación vuestra Vamos
stay there it stays there the first
ahí se queda ahí se queda los primeros
100 I thought I say Well look eh what is
100 pensé digo Pues mira eh lo que se
collected when that happens I am
recoja cuando pasa eso yo me estoy
taking care of myself and I see that it goes up to
tomando la atención y veo que me sube A
17 the drop 10 I take it again again it
17 la baja 10 me la vuelvo a tomar otra
goes up to 21 and
vez suba 21 y
and I was there but I had not given it
y yo estaba ahí pero yo no le había dado
nor I call you at 06 I take a
ni ni te llamo al 06 me tomo una
quick pill eh I call
pastilla rápida eh llamo al
061 I take two fingers of I make myself a
061 me tomo dos dedos de me hago limón
squeezed lemon Ugh it hit the  poor thing
exprimido Uf le dio a la pobre de
suddenly they were all
repente ya estaban todos
in bed and he called 061 I explained what was
acostado y llama al 061 le explico lo
wrong with me he said what pill did you
que me pasa dice que pastilla te has
take I said Well look I explained to
tomado le digo Pues mira le explico al
061 what was wrong with me Well look what
061 lo que me pasa Pues mira lo que me
happened to me is that I was on a live show I was
pasa es que estaba en un directo yo
messing with Javi and Javi appeared he made my
metiéndome con el Javi y apareció Javi
mouth fall That's what
me ha cao la boca Eso es lo que me ha
happened to me oh my God oh my God what I
pasado vaya por Dios vaya por Dios t que
took he says look wait 20
me he tomado dice mira espérate 20
minutes he says and if it doesn't come down he'll
minutos dice y si no se baja vuelve a
take us again
llevarnos otra vez
eh I waited he came down little by little and he
eh esperé se fuei bajando poco a poco y
's breathing calming down I didn't
est respirando tranquilizandome yo ya no
see or hear anything from the space
vi nada ni escuché nada del espacio
eh I don't know what happened next and I don't want to
eh No sé lo que pasó luego ni ni quiero
see it and I have no desire to see it Oh and
verlo ni tengo ganas de verlo Ay y Y
look where he comes out eh
fijaros por dónde sale eh El
This scoundrel is that oh What a
sinvergüenza este es que ay Qué
scoundrel
sinvergüenza
is he a sadist or what s and then
es un sádico o qué s y luego a mí me
this eltra wrote to me he says don't
escribió esta eltra me dice no te
worry that we defended you I said I did
preocupes que te hemos defendido ya digo
n't hear anything then and I don't think I'll
no escuché luego ya nada ni pienso
listen to it
escucharlo
naturally the extra wrote to you to
naturalmente el extra te escribió para
tell you Don't worry  that we have
decirte No te preocupes que te hemos
defended you my mother we are going to
defendido madre mía eso se lo vamos a
ask her extra later eh
preguntar extra luego eh
e
e
eh I F for me one of the p that I had the
eh yo F para mí una de las de las p que
worst time Because besides that
peor me lo he pasado Porque además que
I noticed very bad and and now I can say
me noté muy mal y y ahora sí puedo decir
that Javi Oliveira is the one who has
que que Javi oliveira es la que es el
made me among so many
que me ha me ha hecho entre entre tantos
hitmen around among so many people
sicarios de alrededor entre tanta gente
on Twitter among so many of his that I got
de Twitter entre tantos suyos que yo
sick It's that we have made her sick the
enferme Es que la hemos hecho enferm a
poor thing you don't leave her alone to do her
la pobre no la dejáis sola que haga sus
things
cosas
eh it's that you don't let the woman
eh es que no la dejáis a la mujer que
do her things alone you can let
haga sus cosas sola la podéis dejar que
her do with her money what she sees
ella haga con su dinero lo que ella vea
and with the money that they donate whatever she sees you have to
y con el dinero que donan lo que ya vea
see that you have exposed her eh You don't
hay que ver que la habéis expuesto eh No
let her harass Jabi Oliveira
la dejáis acosar a jabi oliveira
calm down eh you have cut the roll that
tranquila eh la habéis cortado el rollo
I
que yo
sick made poor Manel sick Go
enferme ha enfermar la pobre manel Vete
to hell
a la [__] por
please you have to see eh Yes of course So if you
favor hay que ve eh Sí claro Así que si
want to tell me what
queréis alguna decir lo que qué es lo
happened next I don't know I don't know no
que pasó luego no lo sé No lo sé no
Poor thing
Pobrecita
eh the truth is that  she's telling her truth
eh la verdad que está contando su verdad
eh To continue
eh Para seguir
past Because also it's that I noticed very
pasado Porque además es que me noté muy
bad
mal
and and now I can say
y y ahora sí puedo decir
that
que que Javi oliveira es la que es el
Javi Oliveira is the one who has made me between Between what a cheek eh he can have played with these things He already played with this eh do you remember when to catch her at the moment that to catch her with the 240 He already played with this in
trincar con los 240 Ya jugó con esto en
a space with Pilar Vera irum
un space con la Pilar Vera irum
precisely what a garment also
precisamente que menuda prenda también
no eh in a space with Pilar Verun he
no eh en un space con la Pilar verun se
put on or with Marianela with Marela he
puso o con la marianela con la marela se
started to say like you have to see that
puso a decir como que hay que ver que
she already understood the people who
que ya entendía ella las personas que se
wanted to take their lives among so many people
querían quitar la vida ent tanta gente
on Twitter among so many of hers that I got
de Twitter entre tanto suyos que yo
sick that I got sick little
enferme que yo enferme
weight how good the creature is hands
pesita lo buena que es la criatura manos
go to hell please or how fine like that of course
vete la [__] por favor o qué fina así
So if you want any
claro Así que si queréis alguno
say clear as I was going to listen I
decir claro como iba a escuchar yo
was there for a while he said see Pepa
estuve ahí un rato él decía ver [__]
but I was already with the blood pressure monitor
pero yo ya estaba con el tensiómetro
calling
llamando
061 but yes Manuela these people are scary
061 pero sí Manuela esta gente da miedo
because they are  Sadists
porque son sádicos
enjoy enjoying themselves, enjoying hurting
disfrutan disfrutan con con hacerle daño
people.
a la gente
Oh my love, and of course I was in a
Oh mi amor y yo claro yo estaba en un
more or less safe place, in a space
sitio más o menos seguro en un espacio
where they were talking about something. It's
donde se estaba hablando de una cosa Que
good that I'm interested in learning or
bueno que me interesa conocer o o
starting to learn something, they're not interested in
empezar a aprender algo no le interesa
learning about cryptocurrencies for investments,
aprend de criptomonedas para inversiones
for
para las
investments, and according to
inversiones y según
Elena, according to Elena, well, it seems to me, I
Elena según Elena pues me parece a mí no
can't see you, can you be heard? No, you're not
te puedo a ver se te escucha no no se te
heard, shocked, you're not heard. Oh,
escucha sombrada no se te
well, I've talked a lot,
escucha Uy pues yo he hablado un montón
eh. Don't believe it. Let's
eh No
see, she's speaking, surprised, surprised, I
creas a ver habla asombrada asombrada
was telling you that you can't be heard,
te estaba diciendo que no se te escucha
that you can't be heard. Make yourself comfortable, Peppa,
que no se te escucha ponte cómoda Peppa
don't be uncomfortable. Take off the screen and be
no estés incómoda Quítate la pantalla y
comfortable, so you can move and
estate cómoda que te puedas mover y
do whatever you want, if they
puedas hacer lo que te parezca que si
want to hear the
quieren oír el
space, it's a tremendous shame, man, playing
espacio tremenda vergüenza tío sea jugar
with those topics, eh. They don't have limits, they don't
con esos temas eh No tiene límite no
have any limits, they don't
tienen no tienen límite ninguno no
have any scruples, none, man, I mean, Look at
tienen escrúpulos ninguno tío o sea Mira
their own friends. Look at their own
sus propios amigos Mira sus propios
friends, they put them at 2, out of
amigos los pusieron los de los 2 de los
40, that's what there is. Peppa, the 240 is
40 es lo que hay Peppa lo de los 240 es
what there is, this is what you did and this is what you have,
lo que hay esto lo has hecho tú y esto
okay? And this  you have not
es lo que tienes tú vale Y esto no has
given any explanation or
dado ninguna explicación ni las has
clarified them because this is how it is pppa okay what
aclarado porque esto es así pppa vale lo
you can't do is want to mess
que tú no puedes hacer es querer meterte
with a very well-known youtuber
con un youtuber conocido muy conocido
This is the same as Tania
Esto es lo mismo que la Tania
Exactly the same as Tania what
Exactamente lo mismo que la Tania lo que
you can't do is mess with a
tú no puedes hacer es meterte con un
very well-known youtuber and you're there being a pain in the
youtuber muy conocido y que estás ahí
ass pain in the ass pain in the ass
dando por culo dando por culo dando por
harassing Calling their relatives
culo acosando Llamando a sus familiares
or ex-relatives and interviewing
o ex familiares e entrevistando
any hater and now when the
cualquier hater y ahora cuando el
youtuber responds to you or exposes you because
youtuber te responde o te expone porque
you did something like that okay what you can't do
has hecho tú algo así vale lo que tú no
is want that no no my
puedes hacer es querer que no no mi
sister No if I had done something like that you
herma No si yo hubiera hecho algo así tú
would have been commenting on your
lo hubieras estado comentando en tus
live streams And of course I wouldn't stay with me
directos Y claro que me se me quedaría
because of course it's very serious okay But this
porque claro es muy grave vale Pero esto
is how it is look at what your
es así mira lo Dijeron tus
friends said no eh eh yes a kiss Roman very
amigos no eh eh si un beso Román
handsome was already coming that Monday he will make you The
guapísimo ya venía ese lunes te hac La
donation because even It's that he sent him
donación porque incluso Es que le mandó
to buy food or I don't know what
a comprar la comida o no sé qué la
food for his brother m and he told me that he
comida a su hermano m y me dijo que
was coming in with Agustinita and he said I
estaba entrando con agustinita y me dijo
have the paper here and And it's that he had it
tengo el papel aquí y Y es que lo tenía
there on top of  a table and came from making
ahí encima de una mesa y venía de hacer
the donation apart the association says
La donación aparte la asociación lo dice
if Lamas says it the
si Lamas lo dice lo ha dicho la
association has said it doesn't matter the little note that she
asociación da igual el papelito que ella
wants to send you now is that the
te quiero mandar ahora es que la propia
association itself has said it is that she sent me
asociación lo ha dicho es que me mandó
emails from the association
mensajes de email de la asociación
asking for things that the association has not
pidiéndole cosas que la asociación no lo
done But the association is not going to
ha hecho Per la asociación no va a
lie the association is not going to put now a we are
mentir la asociación no va a poner ahora
sorry Mrs. Pepa Bertrán
un lo sentimos señora [__] bertrán
we apologize publicly because there is no
pedimos perdón públicamente porque no
reason to Because that has been someone who
tiene por qué Porque eso ha sido alguien
hail that sent you it was an email that she
hail que te mand em fue email que ella
sent the association for what For that So that they
le mandó la asociación para qué Para eso
would make a so that they would
Para que hicieran un para que la
support her they would do something that she could get
apoyaran hicieran algo que ella pudiera
out and everything is Well that will be what will
sacar y tod lo est Pues eso será lo que
come to her in January that maybe they have
le llegar enero que a lo mejor le han
told her lady if Christmas of
dicho señora siese la Navidad
course
claro
be okay as she was spending the ch I
sea vale como estab pasando la ch yo
asked girl give me you for this
pregun chica me da ust para esta
call but
llamada pero
not today She was in space again she
no hoy Estaba otr vez en el espacio no
was not bad
estaba mala
re playing with that shame really look at
re jug con eso vergüenza de verdad mira
her and her son himself they also said that she
ella y el propio hijo lo dijeron también
forgot
que se le olvidó
Look for the bone marrow donation they did not
Mira para La donación mdula de no
start donating money She said that
empezaron a donar dinero Ella dijo que
that money forced She said that
ese dinero oblig Ella dijo que
donating  principal se ol
donar princip se ol
Deer with that
Deer con ese
money Dino forgot she said that
dinero olvidó Dino ella dijo que ese
money without any obligation she said
dinero sin que sin obligación ella dijo
that she was going to donate it to the
que lo iba a donar de esto a lo del
cancer thing eh at first she forgot but
cáncer eh en principio se le olvidó pero
at first she forgot and she herself and she will
en principio se le olvidó y ella misma y
tell you No harassment it is not no
te dirá No acoso no es no contenido
sensitive content Peppa Beltrán approximately
sensible Peppa Beltrán aproximadamente
70 years old dedicates this content to me in a
70 años me dedica estos contenidos en
nightgown every day for years despite
camisón cada día durante años a pesar de
having told her no and politely that
haberle dicho no y con educación que por
please stop on several occasions I don't
favor pare en varias ocasiones no me
care about age it is not
importa la edad no es
no eh
no eh
yes
sí
Fran this is Shameless disgusting he is a
Fran este es Sinvergüenza asqueroso es
bad person and you will say Sure but he does
mala persona y tú dirás Claro pero que
n't have to be mean to you from
sea malo contigo no tiene por qué
time to time the
hacerlo conmigo tiempo a tiempo la
person who is capable of this is capable of
persona que es capaz de esto es capaz de
anything Fran and she will tell you Don't you see
cualquier cosa Fran y te dirá No ves que
that aunt was coming for me such that such and such no no no what
la tía ahí venía por mí tal que cual tal
I was doing was defending myself
no no no yo lo que hacía era defenderme
from everything that the boss said
de cada cosa que decía el que jefe
send me an audio if you want
mándame un audio si quieres
and I think this is not about animals
y yo creo que esto no va de animales lo
your thing or anything like that the animals are
tuyo ni nada de eso los animales están
fine the animals are from what I have
bien los animales están por lo que he
understood the otters are already in good
entendido las nutrias ya están en
condition no no  no you didn't know that you
condiciones no no no no sabías que
had to renew Tania is gaining weight
tenías que renovar la Tania engorda la
Pepa's blood pressure is rising because of s Yes
[__] le sube la tensión por culpa s Sí
I'm to blame for everything the the the
yo tengo la culpa de todo
otter's documentation was
la la documentación de las nutria era
from August 2019
desde el agosto del 2019
Well, things can happen to all of us
Bueno pues a todos se nos puede pasar
eh like how how how how in August
eh cómo cómo cómo cómo el agosto del
2019 that renewing
2019 que renovar
the the
la
the otter's documentation was
la la documentación de las nutrias era
from August
desde el agosto del
2019 Well, things can happen to all of us
2019 Bueno pues a todos se nos puede
eh things can happen to all of us
eh a todos se nos pueden pasar cosas
this
esto
what come on let's
qué venga vamos a
[Laughs]
[Risas]
see we can all miss
ver a todos se nos pueden pasar
something what's up man You can't be so
cosa qué eta tío No se puede tener tanta
cheeky man You can't be so cheeky
jeta tío No se puede tener tanta jeta
without more
sin más